<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>No Water, No Life.</name>
  <author>himesama</author>
  <targetVersion>0.18.1722</targetVersion>
  <url>https://github.com/himesama1301/MizuMod</url>
  <description>

for RimWorld B18
mod version 1.5.2

Description

This mod adds "Need Water" to pawns. There are various means to get and transport water, such as: wells, pumps, water pipes, faucets, water cleaners, and more.
This mod should NOT be applied to saved games.

Direct download from github

https://github.com/himesama1301/MizuMod/releases

Please click "Source code (zip)" of the version what you want.
The downloaded zip file contains all the data as well as the source code.

License

This mod includes the following
- Harmony (MIT License)
- ModCheck (LGPL v3.0)

The other files are licensed under the Unlicense. 
https://github.com/himesama1301/MizuMod/blob/master/LICENSE_Unlicense

Contributors

Valerate (VGP_Core and VGP_Gourmet patch)
Dango998 (ChineseSimplified, ChineseTraditional translation)
Firty (PortugueseBrazilian translation)

FAQ

Q1:Is this mod compatible with "Dub's Bad Hygiene"?

A1: In the current version, this mod can run alongside "Dub's Bad Hygiene" however, the two mod do NOT interact with each other.
After a while, I will consider whether I can add compatibility for "Dubs Bad Hygiene".

Q2. Can pawns get water from items added by RimWorld Core and other mods?

A2. It is possible only for the four types of meals (simple, fine, lavish, survival), beer, milk and psychite pekoe included in the RimWorld Core. pawns cannot get water from items added with other mods.

Q3. I'd like to add compatibility for mod named XXX.

A3. In the development schedule of this mod, the priority of adding compatibility to other mods is low (except for Dubs Bad Hygiene). The number of mods for B18 already exceeds 2000 only in Steam Workshop, so it takes a lot of time to just list the mods that need work. Since it takes more time to add compatibility, It is not realistic to do it alone.
Instead, I am prioritizing adding new features and fixing bugs. New features are included in the unstable version. It will not be released to Steam for a while.


(Japanese)

概要

ポーンの要求に水分を追加し、水を得るための様々な手段を追加します。
井戸、ポンプ、水道管、蛇口、浄水器などが追加されます。
このMODを途中から導入することは推奨しません。

githubからダウンロード

https://github.com/himesama1301/MizuMod/releases

欲しいバージョンの"Source code (zip)"をクリックしてください。
ダウンロードしたzipファイルにはソースコードだけでなく全てのデータが含まれています。

ライセンス

このMODには以下のものが含まれています。
- Harmony (MITライセンス)
- ModCheck (LGPL v3.0)

その他のファイルはUnlicenseの下にリリースされています。
https://github.com/himesama1301/MizuMod/blob/master/LICENSE_Unlicense

ご協力

Valerate (VGP_Core and VGP_Gourmet パッチ)
Dango998 (簡体字中国語 翻訳データ)
Firty (ブラジルポルトガル語 翻訳データ)

よくある質問と回答

Q1:このMODは"Dub's Bad Hygiene"と互換性がありますか？

A1:現在のバージョンでは、両方のMODを同時に使えますが、互いに影響し合うことはありません。
しばらく後に、私はDubs Bad Hygieneに対する互換性を追加できないか検討するつもりです。

Q2. RimWorld Coreや他modが追加するアイテムからポーンが水分を得ることは出来ますか？

A2. RimWorld Coreに含まれる4種類の食事(簡単、手の込んだ、豪華、非常食)、ビール、牛乳、サイコイドペコーに限りそれは可能です。他modで追加されるアイテムによって水分を得ることは出来ません。

Q3. XXXというmodに対して互換性を追加してほしいのですが。

A3. このmodの開発スケジュールの中で、他modへの互換性追加作業の優先度は低いです(Dubs Bad Hygieneを除く)。B18用のmodの数はSteamワークショップだけで2000を超えていて、対応が必要なmodを洗い出すだけで大変な時間がかかります。互換性を追加するにはさらに多くの時間が必要となり、私一人でそれを行うのは現実的ではありません。
代わりに、私は新要素追加とバグ修正を優先して行っています。新要素は不安定版に含まれています。しばらくの間、Steamにはリリースされません。

  </description>
</ModMetaData>